Hello everyone, I'm Lin Shu-Zheng.
We are a group of environmentalists who are concerned about the environment.
We have some ideas in the work stage.
We are mainly concerned about the green infrastructure in the geographical map.
We want to add more on the ground.
So based on this motivation, we started this project.
The main problem is that the quality of the land in the park in Taiwan's legal plan has some differences.
Generally, when used, we can't detect the difference in quality.
These are our communication audits around the local government areas.
Part of the cuts Valve made has been raised.
Victoria Youtuber is going to reduce the rules and regulations of implementingено general planning of the 18.
encrypting platform.
and the information flow can be a little bit restrained.
Here, for example, in Taipei,
we use the way of micro-imaging to process
the extraction of information on the surface.
We use the tool called direct-to-direct index NDI
to make a point of entry for analysis.
Here you can see that the black part is the more complex area,
and the white part is where the stone is growing.
Today we use micro-imaging to do time-shifting,
which can analyze the quality of the green land.
We hope to...
We hope to make a hard grasp of the quality of the green land.
Through these three steps, we hope to reveal the information of the green land.
Including the image extraction and the space-time ratio of the land.
What kind of label should be used to define the quality of the land?
And then we will continue to reveal the information.
These things include the space-time ratio,
which is a key point.
How to grasp and form a basic choice for the back office to have a dialogue
is a key point.
Let me talk about the last part.
Here we use the optical image to make a case,
to make a situation of the information.
The green part is the green area in the middle.
It is not the green area of the plan,
but the green area of the plan.
Tell me quickly what kind of people you want to seek.
We don't have time.
We need two people,
including the design and design talent of the narrative website.
And the people who design the landscape with the ecosystem as the starting point.
I hope you can invite the latter half to join us.
Do we need people who grasp the information?
Yes.
We need both the front and back.
Thank you.