I'm a French journalist.
We are working together on a very short web documentary
for French television, TV Saint-Monde.
And we're here just to, well, to film a little bit,
to see how it goes here.
If there's anyone who doesn't want to be filmed,
please let us know.
That's no problem.
In that case, we won't use the footage.
We'll probably going to do some interviews as well.
But it'll be very short, very quick,
because it's a really tiny documentary.
We already met Audrey Tang as well,
who told us about the hackathon.
Sarah was part of the hackathon already in Paris once,
last year.
Last year, yeah.
Yeah.
So, that's it.
So feel free to talk to us.
We're happy to get to know you guys.
Yeah, thanks.
I'll translate.
So, they're French journalists,
and they want to make a documentary.
If there's anyone who doesn't want to be filmed,
please raise your hand.
And we'll probably,
we'll make a sign or something,
and say, don't film.
Just some water.
I'll go stand over there.
Anyone?
Me?
No.
Me, me.
Okay.
And they already interviewed Audrey Tang,
and we'll probably have some short interviews.
We encourage open source,
but we don't force you to do that.
If you can release your footage as open source,
that's fine.
All right, it'll be online.
We'll send you the link.
There's no problem at all.
Yeah.
So just to let you know guys,
that it's really short,
so don't be disappointed that it's not half an hour,
but it's just two minutes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for speaking so much.
The translation was complicated.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.