Okay, cool. So hi everyone, we are Zero Archive.
Hi.
Okay, so Zero Archive is a mission to create a public archive that is storing information.
People in Taiwan are getting in touch on a regular basis.
So we are collecting news reporting from mainstream news websites, videos from YouTube channels, articles from content farms, etc.
So as information is a very broad term, we are focusing our political related information right now.
One of our goals of collecting this information is to study the manipulation of information that targets at our democratic institutions and public opinions.
So what can we do with Zero Archive's data?
Here are some of our initial proposals and we are also looking for people's input.
First, we could develop automated evaluation of information quality to serve as a tool for the general public.
It will also be interesting to see how that quality and kind of information interacts with major events in the society.
We would also like to establish the traceability of information, especially misinformation.
For example, where does some information start from and how does that travel from source to people's chat group, for example, inline.
So some disclosure of our project.
First of all, this is a funded project, but we have not disclosed our fiscal funders yet because we are still evaluating the possible consequences.
As we have updates, we will let the community know.
Secondly, as we are scraping website content, we are not entirely sure of the potential copyright issues and legal concerns.
This is something that we are still researching.
Today we are releasing two data sets.
One is a publication.
Okay.
Thank you.
Then, so who will get the pit master's badge for Wenyi now?
The Pomi? Okay.