automation tools and social network trapping to collect valuable data about your network and one of your challengers.
Basically, the case I propose will be on Taipei City,
but you will see that what you will learn, you will be able to use it for your personal information or goals or projects after this weekend.
So, basically, I will show you how to use this Phantom Buster website.
It's a French startup.
The code is not open, but they have two weeks free trial.
And I don't know, actually, I haven't found any so easy to learn tool in open source.
So, I think it can be useful for anyone to learn how to use those API like LinkedIn Network Booster, Twitter, like you have a lot of tools,
very easy for every kind of social networks and it helps you to collect data and then automate your activity on those social networks.
With no code, it's very easy to use.
So, yeah, in this workshop, you will get upskilled for your personal growth goal, like for community management, marketing on sales and analysis of your market.
And a small bonus, we will probably use Yam, which is another free plugin for Google.
And so, by doing some invitation altogether, you will have credits for sending free emails for your mail campaign for free for one year.
So, yeah, that's it.
And by the way, all the results of my research and also all the results of this social network analysis of Taipei City will be published at the end of January on Medium,
where I publish all my writings of research.
So, keep connected and see you.