Democracy Active Student Group to make a society more democratic.
If you want to know more, look at the leaflet at the entrance, because we don't have enough time.
Our project name is Data Public. As you know, it's a hunched feeling.
Data Public is a raw data archive for critical social issues or public social issues.
Actually, we surround ourselves with tons of information and data, but we don't believe it is true or correct.
So we are just searching for the raw data. If we know the raw data, we can trust each other,
and we can know exactly what is wrong, what is correct, and what is critical. That's why we do Data Public.
Data Public is very simple. You click here, and you can see this page.
You choose this, and you can log in. It's just email and password. That's all.
You're a simple editor and getting raw data.
In the presentation, you can see the guide on how to use Data Public.
We don't have time, but I will show you our vision. Some people say that searching for information or data is like googling or searching for news.
But we hope that you are the first staff to enter Data Public and see the raw data.
We believe that we want to make a vision or a dream come true.
Do you believe that it's important to correct public data to make people trust each other?
Do you want to share your raw data? Please join us.
In case you know your data, please come to our group.
Welcome!