We are going to make an open data portal in Hong Kong.
So to start with, we actually have very small different communities in Hong Kong
that are gathering all kinds of shops and things in different segments of districts in Hong Kong.
So we have spreadsheets and maps, these kinds of data,
but they are all spread out in all different kinds of communities.
So I want to make a united portal, something like that,
to deduplicate and gather around, and most importantly, to weight them.
Because we don't know who to trust in Hong Kong, honestly.
So by weighting them, we could get a grip on what could be trusted on what scale of it,
and then we would publicly publish it on the internet.
So what currently we have is the cooperation from shops,
that we have a few dozen shops that promise to collaborate around to provide support on the list,
and also from the community to provide listings of what data they have gathered around,
and all few partners like me that has the power to do things like this.
So I want to say that because of this tool, when it's born,
it could be utilized by our enemies to attack us.
So it would not be a thing to study in this hackathon on how to counterattack it.
So what I wish is to lower the participate barrier to anonymize how we could have submitted data,
and the standardized data format is very important for us to make a database,
so that it could bore in our scheme or something like that.
And also a reasonable weighting standard,
so that people had an open standard to see why this shop is weighted like this.
And finally, if possible, we would like to lock it in blockchain,
so that the immutable attribute could contribute like that.
So these guys I'm looking for today, so hopefully I could encounter some of you.
Thank you.