If you propose a project, please come forward.
Hello, I'm Ronnie Wong.
Today I want to propose a project called
Disassembling Open Data Consulting Group.
What is Open Data Consulting Group?
Open Data Consulting Group is a group that has been
pushing open data for several years.
We have established a method for
the Open Data Consulting Group.
All the second-level ministries,
such as the Ministry of Interior, Ministry of Foreign Affairs,
and the Cabinet, all need an
Open Data Consulting Group.
There are several key points in the Open Data Consulting Group.
First, in the past,
every season, there was a meeting.
This year, we are changing to hold a meeting every six months.
The number of members of the group
cannot be less than one-third.
The group will also
discuss the Open Data
for the next issue.
The group may propose some ideas
on how to deal with the open data.
Or if the group has any demands,
the government may think that
the group is not suitable for public discussion.
The government must propose
why the group cannot be public
and persuade the members of the group
to tell the public why the group cannot be public.
It sounds like a perfect group.
However,
the members of the group
announced by the Executive Committee
include a procurator
and two retired civil servants
from the Executive Committee.
They are the representatives of the public.
They have a consensus
in the meeting.
They are not so private.
Some of the groups
have never held a meeting
because the Executive Committee
has no established way to hold a meeting.
What is the purpose of this proposal?
It is to disassemble the group.
This group
includes all the second-level groups.
We will open a Google
calculation table for the second-level groups.
We will organize the meetings
and decide who has more meetings
and who has less meetings.
We will add a label for each member
and tell them what kind of member
they are.
We will analyze
the proportion of members
in each group.
This is the proposal.
Let's disassemble
the Open Data Consultation Group.