And when Mrs. Lee had given the idea to her son,
she had watched Mr. Ma along with the kids,
and she didn't...
She didn't see it coming,
but she just felt responsible.
She just wanted to do something big.
She told them she could do it.
She had this big job.
And she wanted to make sure that
they had something good for them.
And this is the key to the whole operation,
she didn't want bad stuff,
and so she pitched the idea himself.
and we are the National Assembly of the Republic of China.
The National Assembly of the Republic of China
was established a year ago,
in February last year.
At that time, as we all know,
President Gao said that today is
a large-scale demonstration in Nanjing, Hunan.
Of course, why is there a large-scale demonstration?
It is because of our excellent
member of the Senate,
and many outstanding
performances.
So we all know
that the Legislative Yuan has a lot of
things to do.
But we are not clear about what the Legislative Yuan
has been doing.
Every four years, we try to imagine
one thing.
We all know that the Legislative Yuan
will be elected in January next year.
If we try to imagine that you will
take two votes, one for the party,
one for the election,
who will I vote for?
I don't know who I will vote for.
The more powerful people may know
that the National Assembly of the Republic of China
is a big party.
But we will see what kind of
attendance records the Legislative Yuan has.
But I can't see what he said.
We may know that the National Assembly of the Republic of China
has a lot of things to do.
But I can't know which
Legislative Yuan has done
what he said.
So we try to solve this matter.
We try to build a
Legislative Yuan information database.
We all know that democracy is not giving,
but participating.
We all know that the people who
are doing these things are usually
others.
Is it possible that we can
try to do something ourselves?
We all know that we want to
reduce the threshold.
So we have a website.
This is the QR code.
You can scan it.
The website is already online.
This website is called
the National Assembly of the Republic of China
Legislative Yuan information database.
I will explain it.
This is the website.
You can see these things
when you search here.
If you click on
find a legislator, you can see
some of the legislators.
For example, Dr. Wu has six videos
and four news.
Of course, our protagonist today,
you can see what kind of videos
he has already shown on it.
This is all from the time we were established
in February last year until now.
We have more than 100 volunteers
who have moved the IBO data out
and posted it.
Some of the people who found the meme
may be the host,
some may be the news record.
Logging in is actually very simple.
The website is already written,
so you can log in with FB
and Google.
After logging in, you can report
videos, news, or inquiries.
One thing I want to point out here
is that we still need a lot of people
to help us
to promote our website.
Thank you.