I'd like to talk about the news bulletin I mentioned earlier.
Some categories were organized in the Hyperlink.
The above is the whole thing.
If you're interested, you can find it.
I'll talk about news analysis today.
I said pearls.
It's just some information.
What I'm worried about most is
that people will make a bunch of information into a bunch of pearls.
Otherwise, it won't be easy to get.
I'll talk about a few categories.
For example, there are PHP and JS.
They are related to quality.
I know a little about journalism, but it's not necessary.
I've taken a few classes, but I don't know much.
For example, I've sorted the page.
This is a small part of it.
For example, the title says this.
You have to make a list of things that say this.
Which day, which brand says this.
There are a few titles that say this.
For example, statistics.
News thief.
This is designed by Roni.
There are a lot of archives.
How many news articles are there in a day?
I don't know.
I hope I can solve this problem.
These words,
they are all strange symbols.
They are all lies.
The archives are here.
They are all downloaded.
A teacher in Taichung
sorted 28 analysis indicators for us last year.
They are all on the Internet.
We can do more detailed sorting.
I said it's pearls.
I see it as pearls.
In other eyes, I see it as mud.
A pile of mud.
What we are doing here
is a left-handed gun.
We don't want to make tanks.
We want to make a left-handed gun.
We want to make it with a single bullet.
At least we have a weapon.
Thank you.