I'm Stefan from Food Sharing Taiwan, which actually is a project to fight food waste
in Taiwan through enabling people to share food peer-to-peer, to have co-operations,
to organize co-operations with food retailers and also to set up public fridges all over
Taiwan.
So far we have a Facebook group and also there's already some reports about us.
So the concept originally is from Germany, where we have this very nice website, which
includes a map.
So the map actually is used to show people where food is available.
So if people want to share food, they can just put it on the map and also when stores
want to share food, they also can put it on a map.
So everything basically is organized through this map.
The only problem is that so far this website just exists in German language.
So as the concept of food sharing becomes more and more popular in other languages,
there's now people working on a food-saving worldwide website, like a multi-language website,
which you can find on foodsaving.world.
So it already exists and it also has this map function.
It is actually open source and it will be coded live and shared on GitHub.
So I'm basically here to spread the word about this project.
So the code and everything is on GitHub.
So for us it's just important to find some more people who might want to help work on
this project, like programmers, developers and coders.
So we even have a blog, which is always up to date and informing about the progress of
the actual status of this website.
And we also have a food-saving roadmap, where we already basically have an idea what will
be the next releases and steps.
So if there's anybody here who might be interested in contributing to this project,
you can just contact us through our Facebook page, Foodsharing Taiwan,
or you can just send an email to foodsharingtaiwan at gmail.com.
Or actually we are also on Slack, so you can find us basically just for Unity on Slack.
So every support is very welcome, so just get in touch with us or just talk to me or
you see me around here today.