So I'm Alex, and this is Nina.
We are from Germany, from Berlin.
We arrived in the end of October, and we had now been waiting for actually this
and we had some time, and in the meantime we tried to adapt a project that we
already started in Berlin to Taiwan.
We were also inspired by saying that democracy needs more programmers or
hackers, developers, of course lots of engaged people in general.
So we thought maybe we can do something about it, and we researched a bit of
Taiwan, and I hope I'm not completely off, but we figured out that from the
hardware that was traditionally going on here, lots of stuff goes to China and
maybe Vietnam, and we read a lot that maybe software could be a solution,
so that it should be more service-oriented.
And we figured also out that in general, in the world, a lot of programming
jobs or computer science-related jobs open, and there's not enough people to
follow these job openings, and we also found some statistics on Taiwan.
Like here it says, for example, this was three years ago, so how many job
openings and how many people come to fill these positions, and now how it's
today.
So yeah, a few more people now are there, but the demand grows faster.
So yeah, we thought maybe we can do something about it.
So we thought, okay, maybe we know some JavaScript, and we already started a
little school in Germany for the refugees, and also we tried with some kids,
and now we have open source and for free, and maybe we can adapt this to teach
people maybe to use the software to make something on top of the hardware,
because this is already present in Taiwan.
And then we thought, okay, what could be the model?
So we checked in the US and Canada, there's a lot of boot camps popping up
everywhere, and they're like 138% market growth.
And now in the US there's like 91 full-time boot camps, and the average
cost, that's the problem, because it would not be for everyone, would be like
around $11,000 in it for 30 weeks.
So translated from the average salary in the States to the average salary in
Taiwan, this would be an average tuition of $2,500 in US dollars in Taiwan.
So we thought, okay, let's create something, and because JavaScript is
kind of growing so fast, and there's like a huge ecosystem of reusable little
models that maybe can be combined to make it easier to build some stuff fast
by reusing open source code that already exists.
So we started actually on the 2nd of this month, making like every day,
not every day, like not on Thursdays, making, can you go back?
So making like all these boot camps, like every day from 7 to 11, we had like
a little free coding lessons, and people just came, and these are just some
pictures from some of the events that we had now a lot in the last 2 weeks,
or 2 and a half, and so all this stuff is open source and it's online.
So we had like back in Berlin this alpha version, which was just we put it
together somehow, it's still visible on wizardamigos.com.
Oh, okay.
So we need collaborators.
Yeah, we need collaborators.
I didn't get it.
Okay, so...
Yeah, please come and ask us if you're interested.
Thanks.
Thank you.