所以惠琦在上面的時候唱了一首歌
然後弄哭很多人
然後今天是來理性的呼籲行動對不對
然後好像上一次OSM的誰有來幫忙
那個Yellow Sword有來嗎
他好像有報名會來
所以應該有些人已經跳坑了
好來
My name is Patrick or Pat Khan
And my project that I'd like to pitch is magic chat portals
So the idea here, the problem that I experience
Is that we like hanging out with people who are like us
And so we form communities with people who are like us
And now there are tools that are very user friendly
And everyone can use them like Slack
But they're all kind of closed off
And they're their own little world
Where you're hanging out with the people who are like you
So the idea is that to kind of create something
Which already partly exists
That makes it so that someone who wants to work together
Between communities in the digital spaces
The homes where people already are
Their own Slack teams, their own IRC channels
Can anyone, whether they're technical or not
Can create a portal that will let them work together
Between communities just as easily as if you ran into someone
At a hackathon and started a conversation
So there's not really much in this presentation
It's mostly just magic chat portals
So the skills that I guess we would be looking for
Is the technical skills, which are not the only ones
It's Go language, it's HTML and CSS
For making pretty user interfaces
To make it less technical
But also documentation and most importantly
People who have communities in the city
Or in Taiwan who are in their own places
And if you would like to help connect them
Then you would be a great example
To attempt to see if this will work for you
So I think this is mostly it
Thank you
You're making universal translator
Yes
Actually it does translate
It translates between languages
And that's part of helping people share space
But it also just brings
It lets people who are in other communities
Talk easily without having to go to someone else's home
From their own home
They can kind of bridge chat channels
So that all the messages go in between
So that's the vision