Hello, I'm Haruseki from Japan, and I'd like to introduce our hackathon right now we are running.
Hello from Japan, and I'm an organizer of Facing the Ocean, also.
And today I'd like to introduce one of my projects, Tokyo Metropolitan Government Coronavirus website.
From this site, you can see the situation about the coronavirus in Tokyo from the graphs, and also the source code is published on the GitHub.
Actually, our website became very popular, and many contributors helped to improve our website.
Thank you very much. Actually, there are many issues, and also many contributors helped to close that issue in one week.
More than 400 issues were closed. Amazing. And we have also other locations.
My edit was deleted, but we have Hokkaido prefecture, and also Aichi prefecture, and also two or three other prefectures are coming using our source code.
And today, the hackathon, we are planning to update the internationalization features and also support other deployments.
There are many prefectures, they want to use our source code.
And also, we have many pull requests already, so we will review the requests and merge it, eliminate those pull requests.
So, if you are interested, please join our Slack, and also I will link this site on the spreadsheet. So, please join our hackathon if you are interested in.
Thank you.