I'm sorry my Mandarin is poor, I have to do it in proper English.
Not really proper, just to introduce ourselves and to tell you who we are.
My name is Karl, this is my colleague Jerome.
I'm from, always from the UK, from London, from BBC,
I'm a technology programmer in the UK.
I'm spending a week here in Taiwan, humbly learning about democracy,
and how the era of the other side of the world, of our own vote,
is actually being revitalised and reformed and countered.
So we're here to try and understand how you all make it,
obviously, in the 21st century, the way that we've been doing it,
combining both the top-down technology and the new way of doing it,
and then we'll go back to the US and the European way of doing it,
making it a country that will be on, well, including all of you,
so on the Italian and the Taiwanese companies,
and Kodal, and JOIN, and VITA1,
and really just trying to understand how we can learn,
what you're doing here, to try and make our own country,
into the 21st century, the next generation.
So, thanks so much, I hope that we can speak to you over the next few hours,
and we've got so much coming up, and it's been hugely welcoming,
and I'm really pleased to be here today, and I look forward to meeting you all,
and I hope you'll join us for the rest of the day.
APPLAUSE